Oh, dude!
Now I'm all covered in soup!
Well, it ain't fit for eating, is it?
Why not wear it?
Hehehehe!
Bring out another barrelful!
We'll have a food fight!
Pour some over here!
There's plenty of food here!
No reason for anyone in Wano to go hungry!
So why do you idiots have all of it?
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
Dream it out
Woah!
This guy is a freak!
He's really into that soup.
Kinda weird.
Yeah, it's damn good.
Nothing in the whole world
tastes as sweet as this.
You don't even want this!
Why do you get to have it
while Dome goes hungry?
Ah!
Woo!
The Rockstar!
Ah!
Hey, Captain, look.
Damn Straw Hats!
The moron can't even follow his own plan!
I thought we were avoiding fights.
Isn't that the whole reason
why we're wearing disguises?
Whatever.
Kid, let him be.
If the idiot wants to make a scene, that
makes it easier for us to pass through.
What the hell?
You couldn't resist, huh?
You really made a mess down here.
I follow the chaos, and what do
you know, it leads straight to you.
What the hell, Luffy?
You're gonna get us killed.
You can't do anything quietly, can you?
Unreal.
Is this how it goes every
time with those fools?
Do you know what they did?
See that soup?
They wasted it all for a laugh.
Red bean soup.
I had no idea that food
could taste so good!
If that's the case, I'll
have to cut them to shreds.
What do we got going on here?
All that for soup?
Any idea why they got so angry?
That crew is hopeless.
I can't work with them.
Well, crap.
Think they're gonna notice this.
We got all those guys riled up way before
the final battle's supposed to start.
Maybe that's true, but it's not
like they know who we are yet.
Well, you satisfied now? Yep.
And so am I.
Let's get out of here!
Yeah!
They're running away!
After them!
What's all that noise?
Don't tell me someone started a fight.
Hmm.
Wait a second.
Uh-oh.
Up-a-boo, chicken!
You queen!
Stop screwing around, we
got something going down!
Do you feel myself? Yo,
yo, yo, I poop, I poop, tell me what
I gotta do, what are we going through,
something's really buggin' you, lay
it on the street, now that's your cue.
That voice.
Check it out, with Udon under your
supervision, no one escapes your prison.
The rats were locked up
tight, no hope in sight.
Check out that brat wearing the Straw Hat.
Huh? Wanna fight?
There's no forgetting that face,
you must have wrecked the place!
Turned your labor camp
into a damn disgrace!
The hell!
Face the facts!
They made a comeback!
Straw Hat Loopy kicking alive!
Pirate Hunter Zoro in overdrive!
So he broke out of prison after all.
This is the Chief Warden.
It seems we finally got through.
I just called to let you
know that all is well.
Before you party, do me a favor,
catch those suckers—make it quick
before they pull a dirty trick!
I see, I see, but if I make them
history, what the hell's that do for me?
Now that you mention it—there's
someone I'm about to get rid of:
uh, a toby robo!
They're gonna
have a bacon slot in their lineup.
their lineup, So, whoever catches
those rats gets a promotion!
The Toby Rope, huh?
If that doesn't motivate
you, I don't know what will!
This one is mine!
That must be Kaido's tower.
Don't get stuck fighting.
We need to push through.
Got it.
These guys are a little
tougher, aren't they?
They're slowing us down. Uh-huh.
I think they've all
got smile fruit powers.
You're gonna feel my
fightin' music, Scratch!
Ah!
Luffy! What the?
Someone punched me?
Wait, I know that guy.
I think he used to be Jaggy's ally.
Slash!
No!
He cut me?
But he doesn't have a blade, and I
couldn't see his line of attack at all.
How the hell does his power work?
Oh, God. Whoa!
Luffy!
Goddamn, you busted their asses.
That was easy.
This is bad.
We gotta get away.
Don't just stand there, you goons.
You got them on the ropes.
Now hurry and finish the job.
You want to be a part
of the Dome Robo or not?
Get to work!
We can't take a beating here.
Not like this.
We need every ounce of strength for Kaido.
They've got us outnumbered.
But that's not all.
They're strong too.
I've got you now!
I'm good now.
Sorry about that, Zoro.
You better be.
There's no point in wearing
these anymore, right?
I guess not.
They're too constricting
anyway. Alright then.
No holding back!
We gotta break through quick!
You got it!
You think it's that easy?
As long as you're in my range,
I can mess you up! Check it out!
So how do we fight that?
Scratch!
Kid, stop!
You'll blow your cover!
Let them know I'm here!
You're going to pay, filthy train.
So much suffering and I owe it all to you.
I'll see you in hell and go!
Hell no!
Get back!
It's Jaggy!
That idiot!
Hey, wait a second, who is that guy?
Oh, hell no! Seriously?
What the shit is Captain Can't do in here?
Like Straw Hat wasn't bad enough already.
What happened in Udon, Babanuki?
How did you screw this up so bad?
You're making me look stupid!
You just couldn't wait to form
that alliance with us, could you?
I made a mistake.
I shouldn't have been so trusting.
I should have known that you were
working as an informant for Kaido.
He was ready for us because
he knew every move we'd make,
and you were the one responsible for that!
You were screwed from the
start, sucker. Oh, yeah?
You thought our alliance was that strong?
Strong enough to take on one
of the four emperors that easy?
Get real, you moron!
Pirate alliances are
sketchy to begin with.
You're seriously out here
expecting a happy ending, huh?
Well, scratch!
Slash!
I gotta admit, for such a
chump, you're hard to kill.
For all the good it does
you, you're a scumbag. Mr.
Queen, we're having a
tough time over here.
I don't know if we can
catch these guys alive.
They're way too slippery.
Then they'll have to die.
RAPEL!
Seems like you guys have a death wish!
I'd be happy to let you ahead!
There he is!
I knew it was killer!
Come on, kid.
We gotta pack it up.
Fighting these thugs isn't
going to accomplish anything.
There's no end to them, that's for sure.
Hey, stay back!
Ah, even if you kill them, they won't
let you be part of the Tobiropo!
Ah-cha-cha!
Ah-cha-cha-cha!
Whoa, stop!
You'll hit us!
Ah-cha-cha!
Get away from it! Shut up!
Somebody stop him!
No way I'm sticking around
for this mess. So long! Peace!
Is that guy part of Kaido's crew?
He's going completely nuts!
He's huge!
Look at that giant even!
Keep smashing archer.
Sure would be a shame if
someone shot you in the back?
Let's go!
Make a dash for the castle!
Ugh, dumb Jaggy!
I knew you'd cause a scene
as soon as you ran off!
Grow up!
I don't think you have any
room to talk, honestly.
Yeah?
And the save goes for you, Roan-Noah!
Those three are hopeless.
Running from the fight?
Not a chance when I got you in my side!
My fighting music's gonna knock you flat!
One more round!
I'll break it down, check it out!
Hey, cover your ears!
Oh, man!
Agh!
I think I've figured it out.
I prove his attacks are only
effective within earshot.
But once you hear him,
it's too late to dodge.
He's fast, so be ready.
Huh? What? Huh?
Well, it's really important,
so listen close. No problem.
Ma-ma-ma-ma.
I just got word from my dear children.
They said their ship is still in
working order, so they'll be here soon.
But wait.
If they're that close, we
should have heard something.
They have to pass through Mogura
Port to enter the island safely.
At the port?
There's a port.
What?
The eastern forces led
by Kin'emon are heading
towards the back entrance of the castle.
Everything is proceeding
according to plan.
Listen well.
I believe we should
modify our plan somewhat.
Not only have we made steady progress,
but it seems that the enemy
has yet to notice our presence.
Therefore, we should
split in two yet again.
The first group will
sneak in from the side of
the Skull Dome and wait
inside for the time being.
Thanks to our disguises, you should
be able to blend in quite easily.
Meanwhile, the second group will sneak
in from the back entrance of the castle.
Once we're both in position,
we can launch a pincer attack.
There's a lot riding on this.
I wonder if Momo's there with Orochi.
Thus, after a few alterations, the
climb continues to progress smoothly.
One moment.
Suddenly, they encounter
an unexpected complication.
What a pity.
The information on the
blueprints was out of date.
The base has expanded.
This part is new.
But if 2,000 soldiers try to cross that
bridge, we'll draw far too much attention.
Hey, Keen Emon, huh?
Look, look, look!
It's a pleasure hall just for me!
It was indeed a pleasure hall, owned
by Black Maria, one of the Toby Roper.
My lovely lady sister is going crazy!
No! Sanji!
Sanji, please!
Sanji!
Sanji, what are we gonna do?
Let me take a small
group and sneak in alone.
We'll rescue Lord Momonosuke while
you take care of the rest, alright?
You haven't said it, but you're
really worried about him, aren't you?
That's fine.
We care about Momo too, I
promise we'll get him back safe.
Don't worry, you and Chia just
focus on beating Kaido, okay?
Madame Nami, Madame Carrot, Shinobu!
I'm grateful.
Honestly, the matter's
been weighing heavy on me.
Stay safe.
Someone's come out of the Pleasure Hall.
Sir Sanji.
I'm guessing he couldn't find any ladies.
After hearing the commotion
that Reef and the others caused,
almost all of Kardo's subordinates were
rushing out of the Pleasure
Hall to investigate.
Invaders! Capture them!
Kill them if you have to!
It's killer!
Hey, hey, hey!
Step up, step up, chumps!
This guy's not that strong!
What is taking so long?
Ha-pa-pa-pa!
Don't you know the story?
Killer ate a defective smile
fruit and became a pleasure!
He ain't got no power!
Ha-pa-pa!
Let's make a deal!
If you eat this little fruit, I'll
give you a chance to save your captain!
What's so funny?!
Don't you dare laugh!
If any bastard laughs at you, I'll
send them straight to hell, understand?
All right.
Jackie, come on!
Stop beating up, dudes, and move it!
Interesting.
So they broke out of the prison in Udon.
Should we catch them won't
be rewarded not worth it.
They're just a couple of rats
Put your efforts into
finding Yamato instead.
That's Kaido's biggest concern right
now, and don't let Sasaki find him first!
Yes, sir.
All right time to clean up what's
taking so long knock them other asses.
They ain't even that strong
Damn it.
Queen, what the hell
are you trying to pull?
You want someone dead, huh?
Well, turns out I do, too.
All right.
No women in the pleasure
hall means no men either.
It is now safe to cross the bridge.
Infiltration team, I wish
you the best of luck.
Nice!
That's the spirit, guys.
My group, follow me! Yes, sir!
Sniper Usopp, AKA Driver Usopp,
this is tank commander issuing
orders to proceed slowly.
with Brachio Tank 5.
We'll max speed with the infantry.
10-4, tank commander chopper good, buddy.
Proceeding forward with maximum slowness.
Keep an eye on the windows of the pleasure
hall there may be a few
people lingering inside.
I'll be vigilant.
If you spy a shadow, that's bad news.
It's awfully noisy out there—move quickly!
Dive into the water.
water
Come on!
Come on, we're almost there!
You bastard.
I'll make you suffer for that king.
Almost there. Yes! Keep climbing!
Why is this the only way to the island?
Not terribly convenient, is it?
As ridiculous as this is,
it's still not as crazy as the
Alliance we're getting roped into.
Oh, it's lickety-loony for sure.
They don't care what Mama's thinking.
She made the call, so deal with it.
Forget about the damn Alliance.
That is not the reason we
came to Wano, remember?
He's right.
Straw Hat made a fool of Mama,
and we can't rest till we've
restored our family's honor.
We'll serve up that bastard's
head on a silver platter.
That's so savage, don't you think?
Well, I've got a better plan.
I'm gonna make Kinda
Love Me a stamp for me!
Shut the hell up, Flampe!
We've arrived at last!
The land of water!
We don't know what's
waiting for us out there.
Weapons ready!
They weren't dead.
They are quite audacious.
Who knows what King might do?
He came back!
You're right!
That's scoundrel!
And at the exact same spot, too!
No! Wait!
That's Marco!
Huh.
I doubt they're here for sightseeing,
so it looks like the Alliance
thing is true after all.
Can't have that, now can we?
All right.
Back down you go.
Phoenix!
Brand!
Not today, you foolish bird!
Are you kidding me?
Oh, no!
Looks like our fruit's falling down again!
Wano may be a different place
by the time you make it back.
Things have been moving and
shaking around here lately.
Got ships falling from
the sky today, do we?
Look up there.
It's been so long, I haven't
seen you since the war, Marco.